Tradu豫o e Sincronia:
Equipe Psicopatas Dexter Brasil.
For www.forom.com
덱스터 지난 이야기
Previously on "Dexter"...
피가 없다
얼마나 아름다운 생각인가
No blood --
What a beautiful idea.
오빠
Brother, I just found
the fucking ice-truck.
나 방금 빌어먹을 냉동트럭을 찾았어
나의 새 친구다
It is my new friend.
내 아파트에 침입해서
나에 대해 알 시간을 들였다
When he broke into my apartment,
he took some time to get to know me --
내 삶
My life, my secrets.
내 비밀들
폴은 이제 여기 안살아요
Paul doesn't live here anymore.
그렇지, 감옥에 있지
근데 아직 나에게 약 2온스를 빚지고 있거든
No shit.
He's in jail. But...
See, he still owes me
for two ounces of blow,
그건 당신이 빚졌다는 뜻이지
which means you owe me.
그 코요테가 돈을 더 요구하는데 전 가진게 없어요
The coyote wanted more money,
and I didn't have it.
불쌍한 놈들
Poor bastards --
평생 모은 돈을 써서 어선 바닥에 끼어와서는
Spend their life savings,
get stuffed into a fishhold.
돈을 못내면
- They can't pay...
- They disappear.
사라지는군요
호르헤 카스티요
Jorge Castillo --
옐리나가 돈을 놓기로 했던 공원에서 멀게나마 가까이 있는 유일한 자다
The only suspect even remotely
close to the park
where Yelina was supposed
to drop the money.
실례합니다
사유지에요
Excuse me.
Private yard.
Sorry, I just assumed
you were Cuban.
미안합니다
쿠바사람인 줄 알았어요
미국사람이죠, 형씨
딱 당신처럼요
American, pal,
just like you.
딱 나처럼
Just like me.
Coo.
Come on.
들어가 있어! 이 거지같은 쿠바 것
Get back in there,
you Cuban piece of shit.
내가 생각보다도 훨씬 잘맞는 커플이다
They're even better-matched
than I thought.
짐승들
Fucking animals.
God bless America.
주여 미국을 축복하소서
Taking the extra time to kill Valerie
may have been ill-advised.
발레리를 죽이느라 시간을 더 들인 것은
무분별한 짓이었을지도 모른다
My life has always been a sequence
of carefully planned moments.
내 삶은 언제나 주의깊게 짜여진 순간들의 연속이었다
하지만 가끔은 위험을 무릅써야할 때가 있다
But sometimes you just have
to take a risk.
Dexter 1x06 Return to Sender
한글자막 : 미드갤 가
'Return to Sender'
Life is so fleeting,
so fragile.
인생은 너무나 덧없다
너무 연약하다
우리가 쉬는 숨결마다 마지막 숨결이 될 가능성이 있다
Every breath the potential
to be our last.
You ready?
준비 됐니?
Can I have
my cereal now?
이제 씨리얼 먹어도 돼요?
우린 모두 나름의 방식대로 슬퍼한다
We all grieve in our own way.
그럼
Sure.
I prefer the 6-year-old
approach.
난 6살짜리의 접근쪽이 더 좋다
게다가 또 하나의 죽음을 수장 시킨다
Yet another I've sent
to a watery grave.
어 아닌가
Well, not quite.
이건 어떠니?
Hey, what about this one?
난 엔젤케익이 좋아
I want angel cake.
엔젤푸드야 바보야 그리고 넌 그거 못먹어
내 생일이야
It's angel food, stupid,
and you don't get a vote.
- It's my birthday.
- Guys.
얘들아
어떻게 됐어?
So how'd it go?
금붕어 밥의 명복을 빕니다
Bob the goldfish --
May he rest in peace.
와서 해결해줘서 고마워
Thanks for coming over and
taking care of this for me.
그건..
Dead stuff...
알아
I know.
가서 앉으세요
일찍 들러준 보답이 나갑니다
Well, go have a seat.
Your treat for coming over early
is on its way.
I don't get birthdays --
The party, the song.
나는 생일을 이해 못하겠다
그 파티, 노래,..
그저 한 해 더 살아있다고 축하하는 건..
Celebrating another year
just being alive feels... forced.
어거지 같다
That one!
That's the one I want.
이거야, 바로 이거야
- Coconut it is.
- I hate coconut.
코코넛, 그래
나는 코코넛 싫어
넌 코코넛 먹어본 적 없어
You've never had coconut.
It's dispatch.
긴급메세지야, 토스트는 싸가야할지도 모르겠네
I might have to
settle for toast to go.
모건입니다
Morgan.
그럼요, 위치는?
Sure, what's the location?
곧 가겠습니다
I'll be right there.
범죄현장
The crime scene.
My crime scene.
내 범죄현장
I shouldn't have killed them both.
I didn't have enough time.
둘 다 죽이는게 아니었다..
시간이 충분하지 못했다
A footprint, a microscopic
drop of blood --
발자국? 미량의 핏방울?
내가 뭘 남긴거지?
What did I leave behind?
불가능해
Impossible.
셋팅 잘돼있지?
희생자 지문은 검색 중이야
Nice place setting, huh?
We're running her prints now.
그가 틀림없다
It had to be him.
He's watching me.
놈이 나를 보고 있었다
덱스?
Dex?
Good.
I.D. the victim.
좋아
희생자 신원은?
You find anything else?
다른 건 뭐 찾은 것 있어?
이거면 됐지, 뭘 더 찾아?
That ain't enough?
Any eyewitnesses?
목격자는?
자네 일이나 해
혈흔이나 신경써
Just do your job.
Worry about the blood.
You gonna answer that?
안받으실 거에요?
This tin can smells like ass.
The sooner you get busy,
이 깡통 속은 냄새가 지독해 모건
네가 빨리 할 수록
누가 이 짓을 했는지 빨리 알아낼 수 있어
the sooner we can finger
who did this.
You heard the man.
들었지?
He dove 100 feet
to bring up the body.
그는 시체를 끌어올리려고 100피트를 잠수했다
He's getting back at me for
not killing that security guard.
경비원을 죽이지 않았다고 앙갚음을 하고 있다
Please tell me this wasn't
the ice-truck killer.
제발 아이스트럭 킬러가 아니라고 해줘요
기자들이 벌써 문을 두드려대고 있어
I've got the press sniffing
outside already.
아니에요, 그 놈 모델이 아닙니다
- No, it's not his M.O.
- We got an I.D. -- Valerie Castillo.
신원확인이 됐어요
발레리 카스티요
남편 호르헤가 여기를 소유하고 있어요
And guess this. Her husband,
Jorge, owns the salvage yard.
그럼 그 남편을 찾아요
Then, try and
track him down.
여기 뭔가를 찾았습니다
Sir, we found something.
You got anything?
뭐 좀 있어요?
멍은 없고
손톱밑에도 아무것도 없어
No bruising.
Nothing under her nails.
저항하지 않았군
She didn't put up a fight.
If she was killed here,
which I doubt,
만약 여기서 살해됐다면,
그런 것 같지 않지만
whoever did it was a real pro.
이 짓을 한 놈은 진짜 프로야
평상시라면 칭찬으로 받아들였을 것이다
Under normal circumstances,
I'd take that as a compliment.
- 지문은?
- 시체엔 없어
- Prints?
- She's clean.
This trailer --
That's another matter.
트레일러는 또 다른 문제지
I don't even want to know
what some of those stains are.
저 얼룩들이 뭔지 알고 싶지도 않아
Yo, Dex, I think
I found something.
이봐 덱스
내가 뭘 찾은 것 같아
- 이거 줌인 좀 해봐
- 배터리가 거의 다 됐어요
Zoom in on this, will you?
- I'm kind of low on batteries here.
- Dude, it'll take, like, two seconds.
2초면 돼
Yo, what's up with you today?
You're throwing off my Chi.
오늘 왜그래?
내 기를 망치고 있어
- You're not Chinese.
- I'm not?
- 선배 중국인 아니잖아요
- 아냐?
여기 봐
Look, right here.
Does that look like
a needle mark to you?
봐 이거 주사자국같지 않아?
It's more like a bug bite,
blemish maybe.
벌레물린 거랑 더 비슷한데요
흉이 졌거나
Yeah...
I guess.
그래.. 그런가
검시관더러 옮겨가라고 해야겠어
I'll let the
coroner bag her.
I'm hungry.
배고파
여긴 정비소가 아니군
This ain't no auto garage.
Oh! Oh, god.
Oh, I didn't need to see that.
볼 필요 없었는데
임시 화장실 본 적 없나 모건?
You never seen
a latrine before, Morgan?
있어요, 실내에서는 말고요
Yeah, just not indoors.
군대가 내게 많은 걸 가르쳐 주었지
Well, the army taught me
a lot of things.
데저트 스톰 시절 얘기가 또 나오겠군
I feel a Desert Storm story
coming on.
사람들이 볼일 볼 구덩이를 파는 것이
Digging holes for people to take
a dump? That was most important.
제일 중요 했지
I'm not really getting that.
이해가 안가요
지위가 어떤지는 상관없어 모건
It doesn't matter how many bars
you got on your collar, Morgan.
- 누구 똥이든지 냄새는 나거든
- 그거지
- Everybody's shit stinks.
- Here we go.
우리 파트너 너무 오래했다
- We were partners a long time.
- From the looks of things,
발레리 카스티요가 나쁜 남편을 둔 것 같군
Valerie Castillo's better half
was knee-deep.
남편인 것 같아?
- You like the husband for this?
- It's always the husband.
언제나 남편이죠
What have you got?
뭔가?
전화번호 같아요
이름이랑.. 마리엘
It looks like a phone number
and a name -- Mariel.
바티스타한테 전화해
그가 적어갈거야
Call it in to Batista.
He can run it down for us.
독스 경사님
Sergeant Doakes!
We heard movement
in the trunk.
트렁크에서 움직임이 있어요
I got it.
내가 할게, 내가 할게
Padre nuestro
que est en los cielos.
Santificado sea tu nombre.
Venga tu reino.
Hgase tu voluntad
en la tierra...
괜찮냐 꼬마?
You all right, kid?
Come on, man.
이리 오거라
No!
섬세하기도 하시지
Subtle.
Maybe you should cuff him.
아예 수갑도 채우지 그래요
Mi hijito, todo est bien.
Te vamos a ayudar.
목을 점점 조여 온다
The noose is tightening.
이렇게 7살짜리 손에 끝나는건가?
This is how it ends -- In the
hands of a 7-year-old?
뎁
Hey, Deb.
I usually like kids.
보통 나는 애들을 좋아한다
Who's the boy?
저 애는 누구야?
지금 아는 건 쿠바인이고 라게르타를 좋아하는 것 같다는 거야
All we got so far
is that he's Cuban
and he seems to
like Laguerta.
뜨거운 트렁크에 오래 갇혀있으면
라게르타도 좋게 보이나봐
Spend enough time
in a hot trunk,
I guess she'd look
good to anybody.
뭐..
Did he... you know?
see anything?
본 거 있대?
I'm not sure.
He's pretty out of it.
잘 모르겠어
애가 어쩔줄을 몰라해
사회복지과에서 사람이 오는 중이야
Social services is on the way.
괜찮아? 인상을 잔득 찌푸리고 있어
You okay? You got a whole
brow thing going on.
모건!
Morgan, bring some water!
물 좀 가져와요!
I love her.
저 여자 너무 좋아
Maybe I should spend some time
in a hot trunk, too.
나도 뜨거운 트렁크에 갇혀있어야 하나봐
깔끔하고 작은 내 거짓말의 세계가 무너지고 있다
My neat little world of lies is
crumbling all around me,
하지만 아무에게도 말할 수 없다
and I can't tell a soul,
especially not Deb.
특히나 뎁에게는
뎁, 이 얘긴 전에 끝냈잖니
- Deb, we've been through this.
- But I have my books. I mean,
읽을 책이 있으니 차에서 기다려도 되고
I could just stay
in the car...
아니면 같이 가도 되고요
...or I can walk
with you guys.
조용히 있을게요
제가 있는 줄도 모를거에요
I promise I'll be quiet.
You won't even know I'm there.
하지만 꿩들은 네가 있는 걸 알아
The pheasants will know
you're there.
덱스는 제 나이때도
- But Dexter was my age when --
- Deb, that's enough.
뎁, 그만해라
로건 가족이 기다리잖아
The Logans are waiting.
Did you pack your swimsuit?
수영복은 챙겼니?
네
- Yes.
- Good girl.
착하구나
집에 왔을때 그 뒤로 재주넘기 하는 걸 보고 싶구나
I want to see that backflip
when we come home.
그래, 차에 나가서 기다리렴
곧 나가마
All right. Go on out to the car.
We'll be there in a sec.
뎁의 말이 맞기는 해요 아빠
She does kind of
have a point, dad.
What we do on these weekends your
sister can never know about.
우리가 이번 주말에 하는 일은
네 동생은 절대 알아선 안되는 거다
Keeping the truth from the people
closest to you is how you'll survive...
가장 가까운 사람들에게 비밀을
감추는 것이 살아남는 방법이다
...and how you'll protect them
if anything ever goes wrong.
그리고 만약 일이 잘못 됐을 때
그들을 보호할 수 있는 방법이지
얘들아 서둘러 학교에 늦겠다
Guys, hurry up. You're gonna
be late for school.
I'm headed to the store. Is there
anything else you want for your party?
가게에서 파티에 더 필요한게 있니?
풍선이 거의 다던데
Balloons aren't much of a list.
괜찮아요 다른 건 필요 없어요
It's okay. It don't need that
other stuff. It's too expensive.
너무 비싸
How about you let me worry
about that stuff, okay?
그런건 엄마가 걱정할게
네 파티 때 원하는 건 다 하렴
It's your party. You can have
whatever you want.
- Hello?
- Hey, babe, it's me.
- 여보세요
- 안녕 자기, 나야
차로 가서 기다려
Go wait in the car.
엄마 왜 저래?
What's wrong with mom?
엄마는 아빠랑 얘기할 때만 저래
She only gets that way when
she's talking to dad.
어이
Hi.
자네들이 보낸 이름 마리엘을 추적할 수 있었는데
I was able to track down that name Mariel
with the number that you called in.
She's a
Cuban refugee.
쿠바인 난민인데 사촌집에 묵고 있어서
차로 데려오게 했어
She's staying with cousins.
I had a cop bring her in.
바닥에 있던 숫자는?
Why scratch the number
in the floor?
사촌
Next of kin, in case something
happened to her.
무슨 일이 생길 걸 대비해서
Guys like Castillo are ruthless.
They prey on families.
카스티요는 아주 무자비했나봐
가족들을 괴롭혔대
He was holding Mariel and six
others captive at a salvage yard.
마리엘이랑 다른 6명을 공터에 가둬뒀었어
그게 정비소를 설명해주네요
That explains the garage.
그리고 가족들이 석방금을 안내면
And if the relatives don't
pay the release fee,
그 코요테가 내다 버리는 거지
the coyote would dump
their ass overboard.
개자식 아주 역겨워
Cocksuckers make me sick.
Come on.
Mariel, estos son mis amigos
que yo te dije.
Sargento Doakes y la detective
Morgan. Puede sentar.
Mariel, when was the last time
you saw Jorge Castillo?
마리엘
호르헤 카스티요를 마지막으로 본 게 언제입니까?
Cundo fue la ultima vez que
t viste a Jorge Castillo?
Cuando me encerr con los otros
despus de bajarnos del barco.
When he locked her and the other refugees up
마리엘과 다른 난민들을 보트에서 꺼낸 후 다시 가둘 때
after pulling them
from the boat.
No tenamos comida ni agua.
Un hombre trat de escapar.
Jorge lo agarr y lo golpe.
물과 음식도 없이 갇혔고
They went without
food and water.
Some guy tried to escape, but
he was beaten by Jorge.
도망치려고 하는 자는 호르헤가 마구 때렸어
어떻게 풀려났대요?
- How'd she get free?
- Cmo escap?
Alguien abri la puerta al garaje.
Y nos escapamos.
Somebody opened the door
to the garage.
누군가 정비소 문을 열어놨대
Cuando los agarren, espero
que los hagan sufrir mucho,
especialmente esa concha
que nos trat como perro.
She said, "when we find them,
우리가 그들을 찾으면 죄값을 치르도록
to make them suffer
for what they did,
고통스럽게 만들어달래
특히 자기를 개처럼 다루던 곤챠를
especially that concha
that treated her like a dog.
곤챠?
아 알겠어요
Concha?
Ah, got you.
제길
와이프도 한통속이었어
Fuck me.
The wife was in on it.
복지과에서 데려간 사내아이를 아는지 물어보세요
Ask if she knows the little boy
social services picked up.
Y quin era el nio pequeo
que estaba con usted?
Qu nio?
Yo nunca vi un nio.
She never saw a boy.
사내애는 본 적이 없대
No hair, no fibers, C.O.D.
exsanguination -- So far, so good.
혈흔 없고 섬유 없고
사인 과다출혈
- You're hovering.
- Keep reading.
- 어슬렁거리는군요
- 계속 읽어
- What am I looking for ?
- Wait for it.
- 뭘 찾아야할지
- 다돼가
This is a prelim.
I don't have time --
예비보고서잖아요
시간도 없는데
M-빌어먹을 99
"M" fucking 99.
에톨핀 하이드로클로라이드?
Etorphine hydrochloride?
몰핀보다 강력한 동물용 진정제
An animal tranquilizer more
powerful than morphine.
It causes total paralysis.
완전한 마비를 일으키지
목에 있는 그 자국이 계속 신경쓰여서
That mark on her neck
kept bugging me,
독극물검사도 시켰지
so I ordered up
a tox screen.
이걸로
마쓰카에겐 도넛 끝이다
That's it. No more doughnuts
for Masuka.
Dude, this stuff is
strictly controlled.
이봐, 이 약물은 엄격하게 통제되는거야
DEA 라이센스가 있어야만 구할 수 있어
The only way to get it is
with a D.E.A. license.
I put a request in
for the list.
그 리스트를 요청했어
아침에 독스한테 줘야지
I should have it for Doakes
in the morning.
Nice.
잘했어요
그래 베이비
Yeah, baby.
I'm on that list,
난 그 리스트에 있다
내가 쓴 그 가명들은 결국 나에게로 돌아올 것이다
and eventually the alias I used
will lead them back to me.
Ticktock.
째깍 째깍
- Hey, you.
- Thank god you're there.
자기
받아서 다행이야
누군가와 정말 이야기하고 싶었어
I really need to talk
with someone.
Everything okay?
- 무슨 일 있어?
- 당신 떠난 다음에 폴이 전화했어
- Paul called after you left.
- Paul? Who's Paul?
- 폴.. 폴이 누구지?
- 전남편이라는 남자
My soon-to-be ex.
He's already out of jail --
벌써 감옥에서 나왔대, 불행히도
이게 믿어져?
Overcrowding.
Can you believe it?
Every time something goes
just a little bit right,
뭔가 좀 잘되가려 할 때마다 매번 이런 일이 생겨
something like this happens.
He wants to come to Astor's party.
애스터의 파티에 와도 되냐고 물었어
- What did you tell him?
- I'd have to think about it.
- 뭐라고 했어?
- 생각해봐야 한다고
But even if I say "no", he won't
listen. He never does.
그렇지만 내가 안된다고 해도 듣지 않았을거야
항상 그래
Can you --
Can you come over tonight?
오늘 밤에 와줄래?
글쎄 일종의 삼엄한 감시 아래 있는 꼴이라
큰 사건이야
I don't know, I'm kind of
under the gun here, big case.
I shouldn't be dumping all this
on you. I'm sorry.
이런 문제를 던져주는게 아니었는데
미안해
아냐 그러지마
No, don't be. Tell you what, I'll
stop by if I can. I promise.
들를 수 있으면 들를게
약속해
응
Okay. I'll keep a plate warm
just in case.
음식은 따뜻하게 해둘게 만약을 위해
고마워 끊을게
Thanks.
Bye.
Check the marinas.
Find Jorge Castillo's boat.
바다를 수색해
호르헤 카스티요의 보트를 찾아
우린 집을 수색할게
We'll search the house.
라게르타는 어디있어요?
Where's Laguerta?
Trying to bring that kid in
for a sketch.
애를 시켜서 몽타주 작성하려고 갔어
몽타주?
Sketch?
사회복지과에 어떤 남자가
나쁜 아줌마한테서 사람들을 구해줬다고 했대
He told social services that some
guy saved him from the bad lady.
Valerie Castillo?
발레리 카스티요?
그 여자가 당연히 받을 것을 받은 것 같군
It sounds like she got exactly
what she had coming to her.
개인적으로는 범인이랑 악수라도 하고 싶어
Personally, I'd shake
this guy's hand.
예 지금은 그러시겠죠
Yeah, you say that now.
남편 여권을 찾았어요
Found his passport.
God...
으웩
이 불한당을 보기만해도 샤워하고 싶어지네요
I feel like I need a shower
just looking at this douche bag.
계속 찾아봐
Well, keep searching.
전화 기록, 은행 계좌, 신용카드 내역
Phone records, bank
accounts, credit cards.
Maybe the wife got greedy,
and that's why he killed her.
어쩌면 아내가 탐욕을 부려서 남편이 죽였는지도 몰라
어쩌면
Maybe.
아침에 공터에서 차 앞에서 왜그런거에요?
This morning at the salvage yard,
what was that thing by the car?
뭐가?
What thing?
트렁크 열기 직전에
절 비켜세우는 것처럼 했잖아요
Before you opened the trunk,
you tried to cockblock me.
내 팀을 돌본 것 뿐이야
I was just looking out
for my team.
선배가 라게르타를 돌봐주는 건 못봤는데요
I didn't see you looking out
for Laguerta.
해달랬으면 했겠지
- I would if she'd asked.
- I didn't ask.
저도 해달랜 적 없어요
좋아
Fine.
Next time,
just get your ass shot.
다음엔 궁둥이에 총알을 맞든가
남편이 도시를 빠져나갔을 가능성도 있어
- It's possible our guy left town.
- If he even did it.
정말 그러기라도 했다면요
카피캣 킬러라면 어떻게 해요
- What if we have a copycat killer?
- That's a bit of a stretch, don't you think?
너무 확대해석하는 거 아냐?
그냥 들어보세요
Just hear me out.
발레리 카스티요를 죽인 자가
What if the person who killed
Valerie Castillo was trying
아이스트럭 킬러처럼 피를 뽑으려다
to bleed her out like
the ice-truck killer
but didn't know how?
- 어떻게 하는 줄 몰랐다면요?
- 발레리는 매춘부가 아니야
She wasn't a hooker.
하지만 다른 장소에서 살해되서
But she was killed
someplace else,
버려지고 무슨 예식처럼 놓여있잖아요
다른 시체들이랑 마찬가지로
dumped and laid out in a ritualistic
manner, just like all the others.
- 토막나지 않은 것만 빼고
- 그래도 목은 갈랐잖아요
Except she wasn't in pieces.
But she had cuts
on her neck.
I'm just saying, with all the media
coverage on the ice-truck killer,
제 말은 언론이
온통 아이스 트럭 킬러에 대해 떠드니까
가능성이 있다는 거죠
it's possible.
What do you suggest, Morgan?
뭘 하자는 건가? 모건
제가 프로파일을 작성할게요
호르헤가 아닌 것에 대비해서요
Let me work up a profile, just
in case Jorge doesn't pan out.
Fine.
Whatever.
좋아, 그러든지
That's the second time you've made
that face. Who are you avoiding?
오늘만 두번째네요
누굴 피하는 거에요?
We got one more stop to make.
들를 곳이 한 군데 더 있어
Nothing lasts forever.
무엇도 영원하지 않다
포드차 핀토에게 물어봐라
Just ask a Ford Pinto.
Eventually, most serial killers
get caught.
거의 모든 연쇄살인범이 결국 잡힌다
There's really not much
of a retirement plan.
은퇴계획이라는 건 거의 없다
But it can't end like this.
It's too soon.
그래도 이렇게 끝날 수는 없다
너무 이르다
I'm not ready.
나는 준비가 안됐어
He saw me.
아이가 나를 봤다
이게 뭐에요?
What's this?
You've been asking who's been
calling. My mom lives here.
누가 전화하는지 계속 물어봤지?
엄마가 여기 살아
Did you forget your laundry?
빨래 잊으셨어요?
She's been on me to stop
by for dinner. So I'm stoppin' by.
와서 저녁먹으라고 계속 그러시는데
그래서 들른거야
And here's the plan.
We go in.
계획이 있어
우린 들어가고, 먹고
치즈케익 나오기 전에 일어난다
We eat. We out before
the cheesecake. You got it?
알겠어?
I'm, what, your
exit strategy?
전 뭐에요, 선배의 탈출전략?
Look, you can stay
out here if you want.
여기 있고 싶으면 있어
나한텐 빨리 일어날 더 좋은 핑계니까
That gives me a better excuse
to leave earlier or...
...you can come in and have
some free food. It's your call.
아니면 들어와서 공짜음식 먹든가
마음대로 해
Shit!
제기랄!
My sisters are here, too.
누이들도 와있어
엿먹을 가족모임!
Fucking family reunion!
그런데 이 존이란 놈이 갑자기 나타나 제 목을 잡았어요
So this john comes out of nowhere.
He's got me by the throat.
전 총을 잡을 수가 없었어요
I can't reach around
and get my gun
그 놈이 젖꼭지에 피어싱을 한게 보였죠
and I see he has
a nipple ring.
I rip that fucker out
like it's a grenade pin.
그 젠장할 것을 확 잡아뜯었어요
M organ!
모건!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Cop mouth.
아 죄송해요, 죄송해요
입이 험해서
우린 익숙해요
We're used to it.
When James graces his family
with this presence.
제임스 님께서 함께 하실 때
Some of us don't work at a bank.
여기 은행에서 일하지 않는 사람이 있어
으이그
Please, first words out of
my baby brother's mouth were,
내 남동생이 처음으로 한 말이
"Got milk, motherfucker".
우유 내놔 이자식아
Oh, okay, now, that's enough,
all of you.
오 됐다
그만해라 모두들
That security guard on the news
is gonna be all right?
뉴스에 났던 경비원은 괜찮겠어?
만약 내가 그런 일을 당했다면
톡톡히 돈 벌이로 이용 하겠어
If someone did a hatchet job
on me like that, I'd cash it all in.
예 토니는 괜찮을거에요
Yeah, Tony's doing okay.
병원에서 인공보철술을 해줄 거에요
The hospital's setting him up
with some prosthetics.
I don't know, he's just got
this spirit about him.
모르겠어요
그는 기백이 있는 건지
The guy's missing body parts
이 남자는 그 아이스트럭 킬러놈한테 팔다리를 잃고도
because of this
ice-truck killer asshole,
그래도 저한테 추근대더라고요
and he's still hitting on me.
그건 남자는 몸에서 딱 한가지 부분만 생각하기 때문이지
That's because men only
think with one body part,
and that one was not cut off.
그리고 그건 안잘렸잖아
엄마?!!
Ma!
진실이지
Well, it's the damn truth.
모건 가자
Morgan, come on.
We got a case to solve.
해결할 사건이 있잖아
정말이냐?
냉장고에 치즈케익이 있는데
Oh, are you sure, honey? I got
some cheesecake in the fridge.
예, 정말이에요
Yeah.
We're sure.
You know...
있죠
I would love
some cheesecake bit.
- 치즈케익이 정말 먹고 싶네요
- 그렇지
차에서 기다리려면 기다려요
마음대로 하세요
You can wait in the car.
That's your call.
He'll wait.
- I'll do the dishes.
- I'll help you.
Ooh, I'm sorry.
I wonder, in time,
if they'll even remember me,
나중에 애들이 나를 기억이나 할까 궁금하다
엄마의 마음을 아프게 한 남자로 기억되겠지
other than the man who broke
their mother's heart.
I'll be breaking
their hearts, too.
아이들의 마음도 아프게 하겠지
He is their father.
쟤네 아빠인데
애들도 아빠가 풀려난 걸 알 권리가 있겠지?
They have a right to know
he's been released, right?
Yeah, sure.
그래, 그렇지
폴한테 오지말라고 하더라도 결국 여기 올거야
Yeah. Even if I tell Paul not to come,
he'll show up here eventually.
I know him.
그를 알아
Everything's been going
so good at work...
직장에서도 모든게 너무나 잘 되가는 중이고
With you.
당신도..
I don't know what to do.
어떻게 해야할지 모르겠어
He's really got a hold on you,
doesn't he?
그가 당신 정말 꼼짝못하게 하는구나
그렇지?
Paul always had a temper,
but when he was using...
폴은 언제나 성격이 불같았지만
약을 할 때는 정말..
내가 그를 떠난다면 우릴 찾아내서
애들을 해치겠다고 했었어
He said if I...
...left, he would find
us and hurt the kids.
Somehow, I thought that by staying,
I was protecting them.
어쩐지 난 내가 머무는게
아이들을 보호하는 거라고 생각했어
Cody doesn't remember
the worst of it, but...
코디는 최악은 기억하지 못하지만
애스터는..
Astor...
She was the one who called
the police the last time.
지난번 경찰에 전화건 것이 애스터야
She was protecting me.
그 애가 날 보호해줬어
You're not that
woman anymore.
당신은 더이상 그 여자가 아니야
그 때보다 더 강해졌어
You're stronger
than that now.
If their dad shows up,
we'll deal with it together.
애들 아빠가 나타나면 함께 해결하자
Dad's coming home?
아빠가 집에 와?
Can he sleep in my room, mom?
Can he, mom?
내 방에서 아빠 자도 돼?
난 여기 있어서도 안된다
I shouldn't even be here.
Rita will be devastated
if I'm arrested.
내가 체포되면 리타는 철저하게 절망할것이다
남편은 마약쟁이에
남자친구는 연쇄살인범..
Her husband was a crackhead,
her boyfriend's a serial killer.
It's kind of hard not
to take that personally.
자기 탓으로 돌리기에 충분하다
Better get inside, son.
Storm's on its way.
안으로 들어오는게 낫겠다 얘야
폭풍이 오고 있어
Why didn't you tell me
what you are, Dex?
오빠가 누군지 왜 나한테 말 안했어 덱스?
마지막으로 할 말은?
Any last words?
없을 줄 알았어
Figures.
나는 나쁜 꿈을 꾸지 않는다
I don't have
bad dreams.
When I sleep,
all of me sleeps.
내가 잘 때는 아주 푹 잠든다
Nothing ever goes bump
in Dexter's night.
덱스터의 밤을 방해하는 것은 없다
I've never felt a
moment of remorse,
나는 한번도 자책이나
의심, 후회를 느낀 적이 없다
doubt,
regret.
What's happening to me?
내게 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까
내가 궁지에 몰리지 않았더라면
If my back wasn't against
the wall, I'd almost feel guilty
마쓰카의 이메일을 해킹하는데
거의 죄책감이 들었을지도 모른다
for hacking into
Masuka's e-mail.
포르노를 전부 넘기니 그 다음은 쉬웠다
Once I got past all the porn,
it was easy.
And there I am.
거기 내가 있었다
닥터 패트릭 베이트맨
Dr. Patrick Bateman --
So wholesome, so inconspicuous.
아주 신중하고 아주 눈길을 끌지 않는
Harry would frown upon
destroying evidence,
해리는 증거를 없애는 데에 눈살을 찌푸리겠지만
내가 잡히는 것도 결코 바라지 않을 것이다
but he never wanted me
to get caught, either.
여기서 뭐해?
What are you doing in here?
내 컴퓨터가 안돼서 이메일 좀 확인하느라고
My computer went down.
I was just checking some e-mail.
이것 좀 봐줄래?
Can you take a look
at this for me?
Copycat killer?
'카피캣 킬러'?
I worked all night
on that profile.
밤새 그 프로파일 만들었어
라게르타에게 주려는데
I'd like to give it to Laguerta, but
I want to make sure it's good enough.
잘 됐나 확인받고 싶어서
영광인걸
I'm honored.
시체를 놓아둔 방식이 비슷한 점에서 이 살인범이
"The similar manner in which the victim's
body was displayed suggests this killer
"feels a connection
to the ice-truck killer,
아이스트럭 킬러와 연결을 느끼고 있다고 시사된다
자기가 하는 짓에 흥분을 느끼고
"excited by what he's doing.
"The cut on the victim's cheek,
while not fatal,
피해자 뺨의 치명적이지 않은 자상은
"appears to be
a signature of sorts.
범인의 서명으로 보인다
"Because of the lack of evidence
collected from the crime scene,
현장에서 수집된 증거가 부족한 점으로 보아
"the suspect may be familiar
용의자는 법집행기관 혹은
"with law enforcement
or forensics procedure."
증거감식과정에 친숙할 것이다
Why'd you quit? You're getting
to the good stuff.
왜 그만읽어?
이제 또 좋은 부분 나온단 말이야
Let me guess --
맞춰볼까
독신 백인남성, 30대 중반
Single white male, mid-30s,
lives alone,
혼자 살며 감정적으로 결여된 사람
disconnected
from his emotions.
좀 교과서적이다
안그래?
It's a little textbook,
don't you think?
그렇지만 이 사건에 완전히 들어맞아
But it totally fits this case.
You're trying to make it fit.
맞추려고 하는 거지
My advice?
내 조언은..
이건 혼자만 알고 있어
Keep this to yourself.
Really?
정말?
뎁, 살인수사과에 있어야하잖아
Deb, you're new to Homicide.
This blows up in your face,
이걸 들이밀면 라게르타한테
그녀가 계속 기다렸던
you've given
Laguerta the excuse
she's been looking for
to send you back to Vice.
너를 매춘단속과로 되돌려보낼 좋은 핑계를 주는거지
아니, 난 여기 뭔가 있는걸 알아
직감적으로
No.
I'm on to something here.
I feel it.
Like one of your hunches.
오빠가 응원해주길 바랬어
Way to have my back.
동생은 어디 있니?
Where's your sister?
데브라!
대체 무슨 짓을 하고 있는거냐?
Debra! What the hell
do you think you're doing?
How did you get into my cabinet?
내 캐비넷에서 어떻게 꺼냈냐?
식료품 저장실 맨위 선반에 열쇠를 두시잖아요
You hide the
key in the pantry...
...on the top shelf.
You and your brother know
너랑 네 오빠는
내 지시와 감독이 있을 때를 제외하고
never
to touch my guns unless
it's under my direct supervision.
절대로 총에 손대면 안되는 걸 알잖아
하지만 아빠
전 정말 조심하고 있었어요
But I was being really careful!
I mean,
캔이랑 병에만 쏘고 있었어요
I was only shooting at
the cans and the bottles.
저도 덱스터만큼 잘 쏴요
And I'm really good,
like Dexter,
이제 우리 다같이 사냥갈 수 있잖아요
and now we can all
go hunting together.
너한테 정말 실망했다 데브라
I'm disappointed in you, Debra.
짐 챙겨라
Grab your things.
진짜 고마워
Thanks a lot.
Starting this morning, we have
cadets from the academy
오늘 아침부터
경찰학교 생도들이 폐차장을 구석구석 수색할거다
going over every inch
of the salvage yard.
절대 그립지 않은 시절이지
Those days I don't miss.
어제 우리가 찾은 아이가
누군가 발레리 카스티요를 유괴하는 것을 봤다
The kid we found yesterday
saw someone abduct Valerie
Castillo from that yard.
꼬마가 호르헤 카스티요의 사진을 알아보지 못했기 때문에
Because he didn't recognize
a photo of Jorge Castillo,
라게르타 부서장님이 몽타주를 작성하려고
아이를 데려오고 있어
Lieutenant Laguerta is bringing
him in to attempt a sketch.
Come on, sweetheart.
가자, 아가야
안전벨트 풀자
Let's take the seatbelt off.
There you go.
Come on.
Come on, sweetheart.
가자 아가
들어가서 좋은 아줌마 안만나?
You want to go inside
to see the nice lady?
가자, 아가야
Come on, sweetie.
Let's go.
데려와줘서 고마워요
Thanks for bringing him by.
Hola, Oscar.
T quieres venir conmigo?
전 보통 이런 건 허락하지 않는 편인데
부서장님은 깊은 인상을 줬어요
Normally, I wouldn't approve
of something like this,
but you've made
quite an impression.
You have kids?
아이가 있으세요?
아뇨
No.
I was like him once --
저도 이 아이 같았어요
전 이방인이었고 낯선 땅에서
낯선 사람들이랑 자라게 남겨졌죠
A stranger in a strange place,
left to grow up
with strangers,
다 더 나은 삶을 위해서였죠
all for a better life.
Well, police lieutenant --
I'd say you've done okay.
그럼 부서장님
잘 해내셨군요
- Any luck with the family?
- No. He talks about an Uncle Roberto.
가족에 관해서는 뭐 좀 있나요?
없어요
로베르토 삼촌에 대해서 얘기하더군요
이름밖에 몰라요
He just uses the first name.
Maybe we'll have
some luck on our end.
운이 좋으면 우리쪽에서 알아낼 수도 있어요
그러길 바래요
I hope so.
이런 아이 또 하나가 입양되는 건 보기 싫거든요
I hate to send another one
of these kids into foster care.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
Bye, sweetheart.
잘가라 아가야
Meanwhile, we'll follow
up on the D.E.A. list
그동안 우리는 M-99 구입자에 대한
DEA 리스트를 철저히 추적한다
of M-99 buyers.
수의사, 의사,
That would include
vets, doctors,
animal control, even circuses.
동물관리인, 서커스조차도 포함된다
빈틈없이, 전부 확인해
Be thorough.
Check everyone.
Masuka, what do we have on
the home and the boat?
마쓰카, 집과 보트에서 알아낸 것이 있나?
아직 작업중입니다
Still processing, sir.
남편이 죽은 것으로 밝혀지면
If it turns up the husband
is a dead end,
새 용의자를 찾아야해
then we're looking at
a new suspect, folks.
Morgan.
모건, 어떻게 생각하나?
Any ideas?
하지마, 뎁
Don't do it, Deb.
나한테 지금 가장 필요없는 것은
The last thing
I need right now
마이애미 중부서 전체에서 프로파일 당하는거야
is to be profiled for
all of Miami metro.
아이스트럭 킬러에게 영감을 받은 살인자를 주목하고 있습니다
We could be looking at
someone who's inspired
by the ice-truck killer.
A copycat.
카피캣이요
범인은 아마도 증거감식과정에
If so, the suspect is probably
familiar with forensic procedures.
익숙한 자로 보입니다
작업하고 있는 프로파일을 보여드리겠습니다
I have a profile. I'd be happy
to show it to you.
연구실에 있을게요
I'll be in my lab.
덱스
Hello, Dex.
오스카
Oscar...
El hombre que viste era
como yo o ms delgado?
Mi hijito, est bien.
Cuntanos.
Cuntanos lo que
t viste esa noche.
금방 올게
- I'll be right back.
- No!
Est bien,
me quedo aqu.
자랄 때 파스텔리또를 얼마나 좋아했는지 잊고 있었어요
I forgot how much I loved
pastelitos growing up.
He just needed
a little reminder of home.
집을 생각나게 해줄 뭔가가 필요했던거야
제가 가족이랑 여기 왔을 때 거의 저 나이였어요
I was barely his age when I came
over with my family.
오는 내내 토하면서 왔어요
I threw up
the whole damn way.
Quieres ms?
Cinco?
Go get the artist. I think
somebody's ready.
몽타주 작성자 데려와
준비 된 것 같아
내 것 좀 남겨놔요
Save me some.
No, dice que no.
Cinco no puede.
Pero tres, s.
- No es 5, es 10.
- 10?
Te digo que t hablas con el seor
cuando el venga, y entonces,
s, yo te doy 10,
lo que t quieras. 20.
30.
- 50?
- 50.
Did you thank Mrs. Carrol
캐롤부인이 학교 끝나고 태워다주실 것 같아?
for picking you up
from school for me?
응
Yes.
So, what do you think?
그럼.. 어떻게 생각해?
괜찮니?
Everything okay?
얘기 해볼래?
You want to talk out it?
홀리랑 블레이크랑 애쉴리가
내 파티에 못온대
Holly, Blake, and Ashley said
they can't come to my party.
아가, 아니야
Honey, that's not true.
저번주에 걔네 엄마들이랑 얘기해놨어
I spoke with their moms last week.
다 코디 잘못이야
It's all Cody's fault.
아빠가 감옥에서 나왔다고 떠들어대잖아
He couldn't keep his mouth shut
about dad getting out of jail.
나 안그랬어!
- Did not!
- You told everyone!
다 말했잖아!
I have to know.
나는 알아야 한다
Dexter...
덱스터?
오 다행이다
Thank god.
팔이 저려요
My arm's asleep.
얼마나 오래 이러고 있었어요?
How long have you
two been like this?
30분
Half an hour.
움직이면 깨울 것 같아서요
I was afraid I'd wake him
if I moved.
그 나이 때는 괜찮아요
At that age, when they're out,
they're out.
그 애 이를 닦아줘도 깨지 않을걸요
You could brush his teeth,
and he wouldn't wake up.
여기요
Here. Lift up his head.
I'll slide this underneath.
머리 밑에 놔두세요
Oh, thanks.
고마워요
여기서 뭐해요?
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting on some lab work.
I had some time to kill.
결과 기다리는 게 있어서요
할 일 없이 시간이 남아요
보세요
Go ahead. We didn't get very far.
He's so tired.
애가 너무 피곤해해서 별로 못했어요
내일은 될거에요
We're gonna pick it up
again tomorrow.
It's only a matter of time
이 조그만 사내가 본 걸 알아내는 건
before we know what
this little guy saw.
시간문제일 뿐이에요
If you, um... here.
만약에
이렇게
도와드릴까요 말까요?
You want help or not?
머리카락인지 뭔지가 렌즈에 붙었어요
I have a hair or something
stuck on my lens.
Luckily, you're in good hands.
운좋게도 전 고등학교 때 안경에서 렌즈로 훈련되어있죠
I traded my glasses in for
contacts in high school.
Boys?
남자애들?
예
Yeah. What I really
needed was tits.
저한테 진짜 필요한 것은 가슴이었죠
난 16 살 때까지 애들 브라를 했어요
I had Winnie the Poohs on my bras
until I was 16. As you can see,
보다시피 많이 변한 건 아니지만
- not a whole lot's changed since then.
- Morgan.
모건
Try not to blink, okay?
깜박이지 않도록 하세요
Okay, okay.
I'll do it.
됐어요, 됐어요
내가 하죠
I'll do it.
뭐 좀 물어볼게요
Let me ask you something.
오빠가 입양된거죠?
Your brother's adopted,
right?
예, 저희 아빠가 범죄현장에서 찾았어요
Yeah, my dad found him
at a crime scene.
서에서는 어떻게 생각했어요?
해리가..
How did the department
feel about Harry getting...
개인적으로 사건에 관련되는데
personally involved in a case?
별 문제 없었던 것 같은데
부모님이 별로 말씀이 없으셔서요
It didn't seem to be a problem.
My parents never talked about it much.
그래도 사내애를 키우는건
Oh, but still, raising a boy,
it's a lot of work, no?
힘들겠죠, 그렇죠?
덱스요?
Dex?
God, no.
아뇨 절대요
말썽은 제가 부렸죠
오빠는 완벽한 애였어요
I got in more trouble than he did.
He was the perfect one.
보인 것 같아요
Here, I think I see it.
됐다
여기 놈이 있군요
There's the bastard.
고마워요
Thanks.
Let me ask you a question.
뭐 좀 여쭤볼게요
Why do you have it in for me?
왜 절 싫어하세요?
You're loud,
you're impulsive, and
당신은 시끄럽고 충동적이고
끊임없이 권한에 시비를 걸죠
you constantly
question authority.
그럴만 하네요
Fair enough.
I hear you have an
interesting theory on --
듣기로 모건경관이 범인에 대해 새 이론을..
Honey, what is it?
아가, 왜그러니?
아가야
Sweetie.
죄송해요
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
- 괜찮아
- 사고였어요
괜찮아
It's all right.
These things happen.
이런 일도 있는거야
Go get changed,
and I'll fix the bed.
옷 갈아입고 와
침대 갈아줄게
엄마?
Mommy?
Is it okay if
I didn't have my party?
나 생일파티 안해도 괜찮아요?
아이가 그날 밤 폐차장에서 본 남자를
경찰에 알려주는건
It's only a matter of time
before that boy finishes telling
the police who he saw that
night at the salvage yard --
시간 문제일 뿐이다
나라고
Me.
몽타주 작성이 끝나는 순간
숨을 곳은 남지 않는다
Once the sketch is finished,
there will be no place left to hide.
내가 살아남을 가능성을 바란다면
전부를 없애버려야 한다
If I want any chance of survival,
I have to get rid of it all.
놓아주어야 한다
I have to let go.
알렉스 티몬스
Alex Timmons --
Sniper.
저격범
Yes, I did it. Is that
what you want to hear?
그래, 내가 했다
그 말이 듣고 싶나?
짐 마샬
Gene Marshall --
Arsonist.
방화범
산채로 불에 타는 사람을 본 적 있나?
Have you ever watched
someone burned alive?
신디 랜든, 블랙위도우
Cindy Landon --
Black widow.
I'll fuck you
if you let me go.
놓아주면 너랑 자줄게
Such fond memories of them all.
모두에 대한 정말 좋은 기억들..
그들은 자신의 숙명을 나름의 방식으로 받아들였다
They all accepted their fate
in their own way.
이제 나도 같은 일을 할 때이다
Now it's time for me
to do the same.
발레리 카스티요
내 마지막 희생자
Valerie Castillo --
My last victim.
놈은 화나지 않았다
He's not angry. That's not
what this is about.
그래서 이러는 것이 아니다
He's testing me.
나를 시험하고 있다
I was wrong
the whole time.
내내 내가 틀렸었다
My playmate saw an opportunity
내 놀이친구는 날 코너로 몰 기회를 보고
to paint me into a corner
to see if I'd find my way out,
내가 빠져나올 길을 찾는지 알아보려고 한다
if I'd fight to survive.
내가 살아남으려고 싸우는지
잘 보존된 샘플을 가지고 있다면
If you have a
well-preserved sample,
마른 혈액을 옮기는건 상대적으로 쉽다
transferring a dry drop of blood
is relatively easy,
호르헤 카스티요의 지문을 그의 보트에서 떼어내
almost as easy as it was lifting
Jorge Castillo's fingerprints
이 나이프에 옮기는 것 만큼이나 쉽다
from his boat and
putting them on this knife.
Just got off the phone
with the FBI.
FBI랑 통화했어요
이제 어려운 부분이다
Now for the hard part.
I wanted to see what their
computers would spit out.
그 컴퓨터에선 뭐가 나오나 보고 싶었어요
아이스트럭킬러 리스트랑 제 프로파일이랑 교차해서
I cross-referenced my profile
with the ice-truck killer list.
11명이 일치했어요
11 new hits.
How about we hold off till
we get a sketch,
몽타주를 얻을 때까지 기다려보는 건 어떤가?
take it from there.
I know, I know. I want to get
a head start on this.
알아요 알아..
그냥 유리하게 시작하고 싶었어요
We could look these over
at lunch -- My treat.
점심먹으면서 이걸 살펴볼 수도 있어요
제가 살게요
You never give up,
do you?
포기를 모르는군 자네
Thank your mom for dinner
the other night.
저녁식사 감사했다고 어머니께 전해주세요
Can't remember
the last time
가족이 절 좋아하는 남자를
언제 마지막으로 만났는지 기억할 수도 없네요
I met a guy's family
and they actually liked me.
자네도 만만치 않았어
You held your own.
대개 우리 누나들이랑 있으면 말도 꺼내기 힘들어 하는데
Most people don't get
a dirty word in edgewise
with my sisters around the table.
우리 집에서 매주 목요일 저녁은
팬케익의 날이었어요
In our house, every Thursday
night was pancake night --
모건집안 전통이죠
A Morgan tradition.
그런게 그리워요
I miss that kind
of stuff, you know?
뭔가 찾았어
I found something.
아내의 피, 확실해?
The wife's blood?
You're sure?
이건 카스티요 침실 바구니에서 나온 거에요
This was found in the Castillo's
bedroom hamper.
We check all the clothing items
that come in.
제가 기다리던 섬유제품들 중에서죠
가끔 그 부피때문에 시간이 걸려요
Sometimes because of sheer
volume, that takes time.
아무것도 증명하는 건 없어요
It doesn't prove anything.
이것만으로는 아니지
Not by itself but
그날 아침에 찍은 비디오를 다시 봤는데
I've been re-examining the video
footage I took from that morning.
Notice the cuts along
the carotid arteries.
경동맥 절단을 보면 길고 깊어서
They're long, deep.
발레리 카스티요는 몇 분만에 출혈로 죽었어요
Valerie Castillo bled to death
in minutes.
- 그럴리가!
- 이 짓을 저지른 사람은
No shit.
The person who did this
아이스트럭 킬러를 따라하는게 아니었어요
그는.. 서두르고 있었어요
wasn't trying to emulate
the ice-truck killer. He was...
in a hurry.
He was probably afraid
of getting caught.
잡히는 걸 두려워했겠죠
살인범은 거의 다 그래
Most killers are.
이게 카피캣이었다면 서두르지 않을 거라는 것 빼고
Except if this was a copycat,
he wouldn't be in a rush.
He would savor his first kill.
첫번째 칼질에도 발레리를 살려뒀겠지
발레리 카스티요의 죽음의 정확한 순간을 조절했겠지
He would control the precise moment
Valerie Castillo died instead of
그냥 이렇게 피흘리게 두기 보다는
just letting
her bleed out.
이건 전부 너무..
This is all too...
passive.
소극적이야
남편은 완전히 배제한거에요?
Have you completely ruled out
the husband?
Why are you doing this?
왜 이러는 거야?
아이는 어떤 사진에서도
호르헤카스티요를 알아보지 못했어
The boy said he didn't recognize
Jorge Castillo in any of the photos.
폐차장에서 트렁크안에 몇일이나 갇혀있던
Well, he was a dehydrated and
traumatized 7-year-old
탈수되고 충격받은 7살짜리였지
left to fend for himself
for days in a salvage yard.
정말 남편인 것 같나?
You really think it's the husband?
심해낚시꾼이에요
틀림없이 칼을 어떻게 쓰는지 알지요
He's a deep-sea fisherman.
Most know how to use a knife.
게다가 아직도 실종상태고요
Plus, he's still missing.
공터 수색은 끝냈나요?
Have you finished your search
of the salvage yard?
다시 공터에 사람을 보내지
I'll have them send
the cadets out again.
이봐, 미안해
Hey, I'm sorry.
네가 프로파일에 얼마나 열심이었는지 알아
I know how hard you worked
on that profile.
아니 덱스
전혀 그렇지 않을걸
No, Dex, I really
don't think you do.
얼마동안 외출금지야?
How long are you grounded for?
Two months.
2달
Deb, I had to tell him.
뎁, 말씀드려야만 했어
아니 덱스, 그럴 필요 없었어
입 닥치고 있을 수도 있었지
No, Dex, you didn't.
You could have kept
your fucking mouth shut.
아빠는 네 걱정을 많이 하셨어
나도 그렇고
Dad was worried about you,
and so was I.
Well, now you can spend
more time together.
이제 둘이 오붓하게 보내겠네
난 바보가 아냐 덱스터
언제나 오빠가 원하는 대로야
I'm not stupid, Dexter.
That's always what you wanted.
아냐, 안그래
No, it's not.
뎁, 넌 내 동생이야
Deb, you're my sister.
No, I am not.
And he is my father!
아니야
그리고 내 아빠야
There are so many times,
I swear, Dexter,
맹세코 덱스터
얼마나 여러번
아빠가 널 데려오지 않았기를 바라는지 몰라
I wish he wouldn't
have brought you home!
Dexter, I am...
so sorry.
덱스터, 정말 미안해
진심이 아니었어
I really... really didn't
mean it like that.
받아
Here.
갖고싶을지도 몰라서
I thought you might want that.
어쨌든 나보다 잘쐈어
You're a better shot
than me anyway.
- 여보세요
- 폴, 나야
- Hello?
- Paul, hey, it's me.
할 얘기가 있어..
당신이 애스터 보고 싶어하는 거 알아
- Look, we need to talk.
- Sure thing.
I know you want to see Astor, but, I mean,
애들은 지금 너무 잘 지내고 있고
the kids are doing so well now.
당신이 파티에 안오는게 좋을 것 같아
Maybe -- Maybe it would be
a good idea if you...
...don't come to the party.
- I just want...
- She is my daughter, too, Rita.
내 딸이기도 해, 리타
나도 거기 있을 권리가 있어
I have every
right to be there.
You know what?
I'm sorry.
미안해, 미안하지만
내가 양육권을 전권 가지고 있고
I'm sorry, but I have
full custody now,
이제 당신은 그렇게 불쑥 들를 수 없어
and you can't just drop in
on us like this anymore.
접근금지명령을 확인해봤는데 아직도 유효해
Now, I checked and the restraining
order is still in effect.
그러니 집안에 한 발짝만 들여놓으면
첫번째로 경찰서에 전화할거고
So if you step one foot
on this property,
the first call I'm gonna
make is to the police.
두번째로 당신 가석방 담당관한테 전화할거야
The second call is
to your parole officer.
경사님 불러
I need the sergeant.
모건입니다
Morgan.
갈게요
I'll be right there.
Est listo.
Ya lo tir.
오스카지토!
Oscarsito.
로베르토 삼촌!
Ito Roberto!
아이 삼촌이 아침에 전화를 했어요
탬퍼에 산답니다
The uncle called our office
this morning. He lives in Tampa.
잘됐네요 가족과 함께 있어야해요
That's great.
He should be with family.
집에 데려가도 될까요?
Can I take him home?
We're good.
괜찮습니다
Thank you.
감사합니다
찾아주셔서 감사합니다
정말 특별한 녀석이에요
Thank you for
finding him, huh?
He's a very special boy.
알아요
I know.
Cudate?
라게르타, 이걸 보셔야겠어요
L.T., you need to see this.
- 괜찮아요?
- 렌즈때문에
- You okay?
- These contacts.
Dios mo.
Wrecks like this are usually
sold for scrap.
이렇게 부서진 차들은 보통 폐차되도록 팔리지
남편이 칼을 안에 숨겨두고 우리가 찾기 전에
The husband stashes
a knife inside
and lets a demo crew
shred the truck
차를 부수게 하는거야
살인무기가 사라지는거지
before we find it.
No more murder weapon.
There's blood.
- 피가 있어요
- 아내 것인가?
Want to bet it's the wife's?
언제나 남편이군요
선배가 쭉 옳았어요
It's always the husband.
You were right all along.
털어버려 모건
살인수사는 시간이 걸리는 법이야
Shake it off, Morgan.
Homicide takes time.
뎁은 날 용서할 것이다, 결국은
그게 뎁이다. 마음 넓고 상냥한
Deb will forgive me...
eventually.
That's who she is --
Bighearted, kind.
나와는 전혀 다르다
Nothing like me.
- 라게르타가 이걸 보래
- 뭔데?
- Laguerta thought you should see this.
- What you got ?
오스카 그 꼬마가 자기가 이 사람을 봤대
That kid Oscar swears
this is who he saw.
개자식!
- Son of a bitch.
- Dex.
덱스..
Okay, I gave them Jorge's sock,
a knife with his prints,
그래
내가 저들에게 호르헤의 양말과
지문 묻은 칼과 아내의 혈흔을 줬다
and a drop of his wife's blood.
그런 3가지 법의학적 증거는
어린애의 그림을 깔아뭉갤 것이다
Forensics trifecta like that
should trump a child's drawing...
그러길 바란다
I hope.
정말 희한하네
- Too fucking weird.
- Jesus Christ saved this kid?
예수그리스도가 꼬마를 구했어?
애 혼자 그 일을 겪고 나면 누가 아니라고 하겠어?
On his own for
as long as Oscar was,
who's to say he didn't?
언제부터 촛불 켜는게 끄는 것보다 더 재밌어진거지?
When did lighting candles become
more fun than blowing them out?
좋은데
Nice turnout.
I called all the moms
to assure them
엄마들에게 전화해서 폴이 나타나지 않을 거라고 확신시켰어
that Paul would not be
making an appearance.
애스터랑 코디가 당신이 아빠를 오지 말란 것 알아?
Do Astor and Cody know that
you told their dad not to come?
선물 다 한 다음에
After presents.
준비됐어?
Ready?
소원 빌어 아가야
아무한테도 말하지 마라, 말하면 안이루어지니까
Make a wish, baby.
Just don't tell anybody,
or it won't come true.
It already came true.
Dad's not here.
소원 이루어졌어
아빠 안왔잖아
- 난 가운데 조각 먹을래
- 그래
- I want the middle piece.
- Okay.
생일에 대해 내가 틀렸던 것 같다
I was wrong about birthdays.
Maybe the reason to celebrate
them is what they offer --
아마도 생일을 축하하는 이유는 생일이 제안하는 것 때문일 것이다
다음 생일을 볼 삶의 희망
The hope of living
to see another one.
뎁이 날 용서하는 문제에 대해서는
며칠 시간을 더 줘야겠다
The thing about
Deb forgiving me --
I better give her
a few more days.
이번에는 잡히기 직전에 겨우 벗어났다
I barely escaped getting
caught this time.
I realize now my days
are numbered.
내 남은 날들이 유한하다는 것을 깨달았다
So I better make
the most of them.
그러니 그것을 최대한 잘 이용하는 것이 낫겠다
그동안 내내
All along, I thought
this was a game
나는 이것이 게임인 줄 알았다
내 분신과 내가 함께 노는..
my alter ego and
I were playing.
하지만 관계는 변한다
But relationships change,
evolve,
진화한다
and this one's getting deep.
그리고 이 관계는 깊어지고 있다
꿈속에서 해리가 말했듯이
Like Harry said in my dream...
...the storm's on its way.
폭풍우가 오고 있다
Dexter 1x06 Return to Sender
한글자막 : 미드갤 가
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Travis
www.forom.com
Tradu豫o e Sincronia:
Equipe Psicopatas Dexter Brasil.